http://domainsdata.org/privacy.html

Domains Data
We Help You Check And Analyze Domains
We have 1,001,751 domains and 4,004,478 unique keywords
Search sites:
By keywords
By countries
Privacy Policy:
PRIVACY AND SECURITY
The statement below outlines the DomainsData.org website Privacy Policy. DomainsData.org may update its Privacy Policy to reflect changes in the products and services that DomainsData.org offers, however, the underlying goal of protecting user privacy remains the same. By using DomainsData.org service, each user consents to the collection, use or disclosure of their Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the DomainsData.org service following the “last-revised” date on this Privacy Policy will represent your consent to the collection, use or disclosure of your Personal Information under this Privacy Policy as modified. You are advised to review this page regularly for any changes.
If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, or feel that DomainsData.org has not complied with the Policy, they should first contact us via contact form.
STORAGE AND USE OF USER INFORMATION
DomainsData.org stores information as described below that could be used to identify users (Personal Information’) on the DomainsData.org servers for the sole purpose of providing the DomainsData.org service to users. DomainsData.org also stores certain non-personally identifiable information using log files.
The following paragraph describes the Personal Information collected on DomainsData.org servers: email address, name and mailing address, telephone number, payment and usage records.
ELIGIBILITY
Use of DomainsData.org web site and all related services by children under the age of 13 is strictly prohibited. DomainsData.org reserves the right to delete, move, edit, refuse to post or take other appropriate action with respect to any messages, information or files which DomainsData.org, in its sole discretion, deems objectionable or otherwise in violafion of the terms and conditions of this Agreement
COOKIES
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the users’ computer or cellular phone tied to information about the user. DomainsData.org uses session ID cookies. However, the user must opt-in to the usage of cookies by indicating that their login credentials be remembered when they login in subsequent sessions. DomainsData.org may also use cookies that are not linked to any Personal Information to store certain preferences about the user’s use of the services. For example, cookies may be used to allow a user to set a preference to skip a verification screen when capturing information.
AGGREGATE INFORMATION
DomainsData.org may use users’ Personal Information to generate aggregated information that does not allow the user to be personally identified or contacted. Aggregated Information shows user activity as a whole rather than on an individual basis and may be used by DomainsData.org to provide insight on the usage of the DomainsData.org services.
DomainsData.org allows third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information.
WEB AND MOBILE INTERNET SITE ACTIVITY
Like most standard Web and mobile internet sites, DomainsData.org stores and uses web server log files. These files include anonymous information about web browsers, such as internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, dateifime stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. Such log files are not linked to Personal Information through the DomainsData.org service.
SHARING
DomainsData.org will not share any information provided by users, except as follows:
Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable) DomainsData.org may use users’ Personal Information to generate aggregated information relating to activity on DomainsData.org-enabled products and services. This aggregate information does not allow the user to be personally identified or contacted and shows user activity as a whole rather than on an individual basis. This information is shared with relevant DomainsData.org customers and partners.
When DomainsData.org Discloses User Information DomainsData.org may share users’ Personal Information with its affiliates, subsidiaries and service providers for the sole purpose of providing the DomainsData.org service to the user, provided that the information is required for and used only for such purpose and provided the information is used in accordance with this Privacy Policy. DomainsData.org will otherwise only release Personal Information to third parties in the following limited circumstances: (i) if a law, regulation, search warrant, subpoena or court order legally requires DomainsData.org to do so; (0) if DomainsData.org’s rights or property or the rights or property of DomainsData.org’s affiliates, subsidiaries, service providers or the users of DomainsData.org’s web site or services are in jeopardy; or (iii) if the personal safety of users of DomainsData.org’s web site or services or other members of the public is in jeopardy.
LINKS
This Web or mobile internet site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that DomainsData.org is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. DomainsData.org encourages its users to be aware when they leave the DomainsData.org site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects Personal Information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by the DomainsData.org web and internet mobile site.
SECURITY
DomainsData.org employs security measures in order to prevent the loss, misuse, unauthorized access, theft and alteration of Personal Information under DomainsData.org’s control. However, no transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. Consequently, DomainsData.org, its affiliates, subsidiaries, service providers and their respective officers, directors, employees and agents do not represent, warrant or guarantee that Personal Information will be protected against misuse, loss or alterations and do not accept any liability for Personal Information submitted to or collected by them nor for your or third parties’ use or misuse of Personal Information,
NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES
Should DomainsData.org decide to change its privacy policy, changes to this privacy statement will be posted on the DomainsData.org web site.
CONTACT INFORMATION
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding DomainsData.org’s privacy policy, please use DomainsData.org contact form.
Contact Us
Privacy Policy
DMCA Policy
Delete Domain
© Copyright 2015-2016 DomainsData. All Rights Reserved.
